cafebritt.com 2019-04-03

# Privacy Policy

###  Privacy Policy 

At Cafe Britt we are committed to **respecting your privacy** and we recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of personal information you share with us. We use the information we collect to process orders and to provide a more personalized shopping experience.

* * *

##### Collecting Information

You can visit us without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. We may track the IP of people who visit us and analyze this data for trends and statistics, but individual users will remain anonymous, unless you voluntarily tell us who you are.

There may be times (such as when you purchase or order a product, subscribe to a service, or participate in contests, sweepstakes or promotions, etc.) at which we ask you to provide certain information about yourself, such as your name, shipping/billing address, telephone number, email address and credit card information. We also maintain a record of your product purchases. Whether or not to provide such information is completely your own choice. But _if you choose not to provide the information we request, we may not be able to process your order_ or provide the services required.

* * *

##### Cookies

Our web site uses "cookies." A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Generally, we use cookies to remind us of who you are, tailor our products and services to suit your personal interests, advertise and communicate diverse Cafe Britt promotions throughout the Internet, learn about your interaction with our products and services, estimate our audience size and analyze your visiting patterns, in order to enhance your shopping experience. _No Personally Identifiable Information_ about your visits to our Website is collected during this process. However, if you do not wish to share this anonymous information you can opt-out by disabling or not allowing cookies in your browser.

* * *

##### Using Information

We use the personal information you provide for internal purposes only, to process and fulfill your order, to notify you of your order status, to fulfill or respond to your request, to inform you of new products, services and offers, to provide you with information about Cafe Britt and advertise diverse Cafe Britt promotions through the internet, to shape our recommendations about coffee or related items that might be of interest to you, and to analyze trends and statistics that will help us develop the design and layout of the website that will make your shopping experience a convenient and useful one. Persons who provide us with their telephone numbers _will only_ be contacted regarding orders or general Customer Service Purposes.

* * *

##### Options we offer to manage your Personal Information.

Cafe Britt ensures, we provide you with best possible way to manage your personal information. Please be sure to indicate your full name, and specifically what information you do not want to receive. If you would like to update or correct your email address, street address or other personal information or opt out from our marketing emails, feel free to follow the instructions provided in our emails or contact us to help you. You can also login to your account at www.cafebritt.com, if you have one and manage your contact details, preferences and to update your personal information. When you order online or by phone, or when you choose to enter a sweepstakes or other promotion, we may need to contact you via email, phone or mail to address questions or issues specific to your order, entry, etc., _even if you have opted to not receive communications_. In this way, we ensure quality service and follow-up. When you opt out from our emails (which you do by clicking the "Unsubscribe" link on our promotions emails), it usually takes up to 48 hours to update our system and exclude you from all promotional emails. Feel free to contact us at 1-800-462-7488 for any further details or any doubts you might have. 

* * *

##### Protecting Children

Cafe Britt takes special care to protect the safety and privacy of children. Our web site is a [General Audience](https://www.truste.org/docs/How_to_Comply_with_COPPA.doc) site. Don't forget, Cafe Britt is a great resource for all kinds of research projects on coffee. We'd love to hear from you and your children. Cafe Britt encourages children under 16 to get their parents’ permission before contacting us or submitting any information to us. Of course, there is nothing better than personal supervision of children while they surf the Internet.

* * *

##### Security

When you place orders or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. Furthermore, all of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access. All your personal information is encrypted before it is transmitted over the Internet. If you prefer not to enter your credit card online, you can call or fax in your credit information after you place your order online. Call us at **1-800-GO-BRITT** (1-800 462-7488) in the US and Canada; or fax us at 1-800-652-5679.

Note: Most banks either cover all the charges that result from unauthorized use of your credit card or limit your liability to US$50, the maximum liability allowed under the Fair Credit Billing Act. You must notify your credit card provider of the unauthorized use in accordance with its reporting rules and procedures.

* * *

##### Disclosure to Outside Third Parties

**Cafe Britt respects your privacy**. Any information you give us is held with the utmost care and security. However, Cafe Britt may share non-personal aggregate, or summary, information regarding its customers with partners or other third parties. The information that you give us and information about your order may be combined with other personally identifiable information (such as demographic information and past purchase history) available from our records and other sources. This information will be used to make our future marketing efforts more efficient. This information may also be shared with our third party service providers that assist us with our marketing efforts and with other marketers whose products or services we feel may be of interest to you. If you prefer that we do not share your name and address with other marketers, please email us at [info@cafebritt.com](mailto:info@cafebritt.com). Cafe Britt cannot control and thus assumes no responsibility in relation with the use third parties may give to information they collect in contests run as co-promotions.

* * *

We didn't use the OpenSSL in CafeBritt.com. As a result, HeartBleed does not present a risk to our web properties and more importantly our customer data.

##### Your Feedback

Help us improve our privacy policy and practice. We are eager to hear from you and encourage you to email us with your questions or comments. **We read and respond to every email we receive** within 24 hours. You may email us at [info@cafebritt.com](mailto:info@cafebritt.com) or call us at **1-800-GO-BRITT** (1-800-462-7488)
